[{"question": " well that&#146;s no way to sell newspapers. why don&#146;t you try, &quot;extra! extra! read all about it!&quot;", "answer": " no, monica&#146;s restaurant got a horrible review in the post.  i didn&#146;t want her to see it, so i ran around the neighborhood and bought all the copies i could find.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " man, this is bad! and i&#146;ve had my share of bad reviews. i still remember my first good one though.  &quot;everything else in this production of our town was simply terrible. joey tribbiani was abysmal.&quot;", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": "  oh my god! look at all the newspapers! it must be a good review! is it great?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " umm&#133;", "answer": "  oh dear god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " but the good news is, no one in a two-block radius will ever know.", "answer": " what about the rest of manhattan?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " yeah, they all know.", "answer": " oh my god, this is horrible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i&#146;m so sorry.", "answer": " i&#146;m so humiliated!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yeah but y&#146;know what they say mon, &quot;there&#146;s no such thing as bad press.&quot;", "answer": " you don&#146;t think that umm,  &quot;the chef&#146;s mahi mahi was awful awful,&quot; is bad press?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " i didn&#146;t write it.", "answer": " is he right? am i really&#151;am i awful?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " yeah! yeah monica! you listen to me, okay? and i&#146;m not just saying this because i&#146;m your friend, i&#146;m sayin&#146; it &#145;cause it&#146;s the truth. you&#146;re food is abysmal!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " ross!", "answer": "  what?! what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " i am freaking out!", "answer": " are ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " my due date is in one week!", "answer": " what are you doing up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " that is seven days!", "answer": " okay look, i had a lot of water before i went to bed. can we do this after&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  no-no-no-no-no ross! please, come on we do not have any of the big stuff we need! we do not a changing table! we do not have a crib! we do not have a diaper service!", "answer": " it&#146;s funny you should mention diapers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " i&#146;m serious.", "answer": " okay look, there&#146;s nothing to worry about. we have plenty of time. there&#146;s a great baby furniture store on west 10th. tomorrow, we will go there and we will get you everything that you need. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " okay. thank you. that&#146;s great. thank you. wait-wait! where on west 10th? because there&#146;s this really cute shoe store that has like this little&#133;", "answer": "  okay. okay. if uh, if you&#146;re gonna do this, then i&#146;m gonna do that.  so&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  oh, wait ross! i&#146;m sorry, one more thing!", "answer": "  yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " umm, our situation. y&#146;know umm, what we mean to each other. and i mean we-we&#146;re having this baby together, and we live together. isn&#146;t that, isn&#146;t that weird?", "answer": "   well uh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " monica and chandler's, monica is cooking as chandler looks on.", "answer": "  hey uh monica, i can&#146;t remember. did we say we were gonna meet here or at the movies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " we said at the movies, but&#133;", "answer": " okay, i&#146;ll see you there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " joey!  now that you&#146;re here&#133;", "answer": " sure, i can hang out &#145;til i have to meet ya.  what uh&#151;how come you&#146;re not going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i have a job interview i have to get ready for.", "answer": " i thought you already have a job.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " and people say you don&#146;t pay attention. no, this is a much better job. it&#146;s vice-president of a company that does data reconfiguration and statistical factoring for other companies.", "answer": " wow! how do you know how to do that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " that&#146;s what i do now.", "answer": " hey joey, come taste this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " what is it?", "answer": " remember that guy that gave me a bad review? well&#133;  i&#146;m getting my revenge!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " you cooked him?", "answer": " no. he teaches a course on food criticism at the new school, so before we go to the movies i wanna go by there and make him try my bollet base again. oh, i cannot wait to read the front page of the post tomorrow! &quot;restaurant reviewer admits: i was wrong about monica.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " do you uh, want these things delivered mr. and mrs. geller?", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " no-no-no! no, no, no, we&#146;re not married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " we are having a baby together, but we&#146;re not involved.  i mean, uh we-we were seeing each other a while ago, but then we were just friends. and then there was one drunken night.  or, yes stranger, we&#146;d like this delivered please.", "answer": " why don&#146;t you fill out this address card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " oh, okay.", "answer": " i notice you picked out a lot of our dinosaur items.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh yeah! actually, that&#146;s one of the reasons why we&#146;re not a couple.", "answer": " i chose those, i&#146;m a paleontologist.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " really?! that is so cool!", "answer": " oh. oh yeah, don&#146;t get to worked up over it. i mean it-it sounds like he&#146;s a doctor, but he&#146;s not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " oh no-no, i&#146;m fascinated by paleontology. have you read the new walter alvarez book?", "answer": " yeah! i-i teach it in my class.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh my god! i&#146;m standing at a cash register, holding a credit card, and i&#146;m bored.", "answer": "  oh, i love your neighborhood. there&#146;s a great gym right around the corner from your building.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " that&#146;s my gym.", "answer": " i can tell you work out.  a paleontologist who works out, you&#146;re like indiana jones.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hi pheebs!", "answer": " hey! oh, how did baby shopping go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, it was great! we got everything that we needed! oh and ross, almost got something that wasn&#146;t on the list. a whore.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " well, we were paying for our stuff and this saleswoman just started flirting with him.", "answer": " well did she know you two weren&#146;t married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh my god! well the idea of a woman flirting with a-with a single man, we-we must alert the church elders!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " you don&#146;t understand! you didn&#146;t see how brazen she was.", "answer": " sounds like you&#146;re a little jealous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no! i&#146;m not! i-i-i just think it&#146;s wrong! it&#146;s-it&#146;s that i&#146;m&#151;here i am about to pop and he&#146;s out picking up some shop girl at sluts &#145;r&#146; us!", "answer": " is that a real place?  are they hiring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": "  hey phoebe!  fatty!", "answer": " hey chandler, why so fancy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " well, i got a job interview. it&#146;s kinda a big deal too. its a lot more money and i&#146;d be doing data reconfiguration and statistical factoring.", "answer": " wait, i think i know someone who does that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " me! i do that. so&#133; seriously, do i look okay? i&#146;m little nervous.", "answer": " oh yeah! you really&#151;you look great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah, just don&#146;t get your hopes up.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " well, the interview&#133;", "answer": " what about it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " y&#146;know! you don&#146;t make a very good first impression.", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh you don&#146;t know.", "answer": " are you serious?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " yes, when i first met you, you were like, &quot;blah, blah, blah.&quot; i was like, shhh!", "answer": " what is it that i do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " well it&#146;s just like you&#146;re trying too hard. always making jokes, y&#146;know, you just&#151;you come off a little needy.", "answer": "  did you like me when we first met?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hi! umm, i&#146;m monica geller, i&#146;m the chef at alessandro&#146;s. the food critic: still?", "answer": " i think the things that you said about me are really unfair, and i would like for you to give my boule base another chance. the food critic: i don&#146;t see any reason why i would do that to myself again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " either eat it, or be in it.", "answer": " spoon?  so, what do you think? the food critic: i&#146;m torn, between my integrity and my desire to avoid a beating. but i must be honest, your soap is abysmal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i can. the cooking teacher: okay, go ahead.", "answer": " well umm, they both have a egg yolk and butter base, but a bournese has shallots, shirvel, and most importantly teradyne. the cooking teacher: that&#146;s very good, what&#146;s your name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " monica. the cooking teacher: monica, you go to the head of the class.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " all this stuff takes up a lot of room. hey how uh, how serious are you about keeping ben in your life?", "answer": " my son? pretty serious.  oh hey katie!  what uh, what are you doing here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " ah, must&#146;ve been fairly obvious since it was the only thing left in your store.", "answer": " listen, to be honest, home deliveries are really a part of my job description.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh uh&#133;i actually came here to ask you out.", "answer": " oh! wow! uh, yeah! that sounds great. i&#146;m just gonna put this  back in my pocket, pretend that didn&#146;t happen. uh yeah, actually i&#146;m free now. do you wanna grab some coffee or&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " sure!", "answer": " horny bitch.  no! you&#146;re a horny bitch! noooo! you&#146;re the horny bitch! no! you&#146;re a horny bitch! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " so you guys go, have a really good time.", "answer": "  yeah, i&#146;m just gonna grab my coat. and uh, and my whip.  y&#146;know because of the indiana jones?  not-not because i&#146;m-i&#146;m into s&amp;m.  i&#146;m not-i&#146;m not into anything weird. y&#146;know? just-just normal sex.  so, i&#146;m gonna grab my coat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " so, you had a good day huh? big commission; picked up a daddy.", "answer": " are you okay with this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh yeah! yeah please, you guys have fun.", "answer": " okay. it was nice to see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " oh and it was great to see you too. and you look fantastic, although you missed a button.", "answer": " oh umm, actually i umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " i can&#146;t even believe this! i really come off that badly?", "answer": " oh! it&#146;s okay, you calm down after a while and then people can see how really sweet and wonderful you really are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " oh good. good, because i&#146;m sure this interview is gonna last a couple of weeks.", "answer": " all right, don&#146;t freak out! okay? i-i will help you. how long before you have to leave?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " an hour.", "answer": " i can&#146;t help you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " phoebe!", "answer": " all right, all right, we&#146;ll just do our best. okay? so let&#146;s say i&#146;m the interviewer and i&#146;m meeting you for the first time. okay. &quot;hi! come on in, i&#146;m uh, regina philange.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " chandler bing.", "answer": " bing, what an unusual name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " hi. the cooking teacher: your fettuccini alfredo looks a little dry, did you use all your cheese?", "answer": " when you say used, do you mean eat as a pre-cooking snack? the cooking teacher: and the cream?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " cheese makes me thirsty. the cooking teacher: okay. let&#146;s move on.", "answer": " all right. the cooking teacher:  oh! something smells good over at monica&#146;s station!  oh my god! this is absolutely amazing! you&#146;ve never made this before?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh no! i don&#146;t know anything about cooking. i had to ask someone what it&#146;s called when the, when the water makes those little bubbles. the cooking teacher: well, hats off to the chef.", "answer": " i-i-i&#146;m sorry, your-your mouth was full, i didn&#146;t hear what you said. umm, hats off to who now? the cooking teacher: the chef!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " &#133;i think you&#146;ll find if i come to work here, i don&#146;t micro-manage. i don&#146;t shy away from delegating.", "answer": " um-hmm, that&#146;s good to know. but let&#146;s stop focusing on what you don&#146;t do, and start focusing on what you do do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  what i do do&#133;is manage to uh, create an atmosphere of support for the people working with me.", "answer": " i see. nice sidestep on the do do thing by the way.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hardest thing i&#146;ve ever done in my life.", "answer": " you gotta go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " okay, don&#146;t worry. you&#146;re ready.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " absolutely! just fight all your natural instincts and you&#146;ll be great.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ah monica, my star student.", "answer": " y&#146;know, you called me that before so i-i took the liberty of fashioning a star out of aluminum foil. now, no pressure, you like my cookies, you give me the star.  the cooking teacher:  oh, yum-yum-yum.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " wow! a star!  i know you all hate me and-and i&#146;m sorry, but i don&#146;t care.  the cooking teacher: okay joey, you&#146;re up next.  this are good! this is amazing! you get an a!", "answer": " i can an a? in-in school?  hey, i&#146;m a dork.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " joey! i&#146;m so proud of you! the cooking teacher: i think you should give him your star.", "answer": " excuse me? he doesn&#146;t even know what he&#146;s doing! the cooking teacher: we&#146;re all beginners here. nobody knows what they&#146;re doing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i do! i&#146;m a professional chef!  oh relax! it&#146;s not a courtroom drama! the cooking teacher: if you&#146;re a professional chef, what are you doing taking introduction to cooking?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " i&#146;m-i&#146;m sorry, it&#146;s just that umm&#133; well i-i cook at this restaurant, alessandro&#146;s, and umm i just got a really bad review&#133; the cooking teacher: oh alessandro&#146;s! i love that place!", "answer": " you do? the cooking teacher: oh yes! you&#146;re an excellent chef! as a person you&#146;re a little&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " oh, i&#146;m totally crazy, but you-you like the food? the cooking teacher: very much.", "answer": " okay then, i don&#146;t stink. i&#146;m a good chef. okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! i don&#146;t want to go. i&#146;m having fun. the cooking teacher: well actually, did either of you pay for this class?", "answer": " hey-hey-hey, if my friend says it&#146;s time to go, it&#146;s time to go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " &#133;also i was the point person on my company&#146;s transition from the kl-5 to gr-6 system.", "answer": " you must&#146;ve had your hands full.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " that i did. that i did.", "answer": " so let&#146;s talk a little bit about your duties.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  my duties?  all right.", "answer": " now you&#146;ll be heading a whole division, so you&#146;ll have a lot of duties.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": "  i see.", "answer": " but there&#146;ll be perhaps 30 people under you so you can dump a certain amount on them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  good to know.", "answer": " we can go into detail&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no don&#146;t i beg of you!", "answer": " all right then, we&#146;ll have a definite answer for you on monday, but i think i can say with some confidence, you&#146;ll fit in well here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": "  really?!", "answer": " absolutely.  you can relax; you did great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " poo?", "answer": " oh my god this doesn&#146;t count! okay? the interview was over, that was the real chandler bing in there, this is just some crazy guy out in the hall! call security! there&#146;s a crazy guy out in the hall!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " poo?!", "answer": " i&#146;ll look forward to your call.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hi! you&#146;re back from your date!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " how are you?", "answer": " i&#146;m fine, but that&#146;s not important. what&#146;s important is how was she?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " uhh, it was fun. we, we just had coffee.", "answer": " oh uh-huh, uh-huh, coffee, a little rub-rub-rub under the table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " what&#146;s uh, what&#146;s going on? do you not, do you not like katie?", "answer": " no! no, she&#146;s&#151;she was nice. i mean, she&#146;s a little slutty, but who isn&#146;t?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i liked her.", "answer": " of course you did ross, you would date a gorilla if it called you indiana jones!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " did you get like a fresh batch of pregnancy hormones today?!", "answer": " no! it&#146;s just that, kate bothered me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " why? what was wrong with her?", "answer": " there was nothing wrong with her! all right? she was perfectly lovely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " okay, so what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " i don&#146;t want you to date her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  why? what, what are you jealous?", "answer": " yes! and not because i want you to go out with me, but because i don&#146;t want you to go out with anybody! okay? i know it&#146;s a terrible thing to even think this, and it&#146;s completely inappropriate, but i want you to be at my constant beck and call 24 hours a day! i&#146;m very sorry, but that is just the way that i feel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i won&#146;t date. i&#146;ll uh, i&#146;ll be here, with you, all the time.", "answer": " really? but i&#146;m being so unreasonable.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " do you feel better?", "answer": " no, not really. you&#146;re pressing the baby into my bladder and now i have to pee. sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " uh rach?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " just one thing umm&#133;", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " we live together. you&#146;re having our baby. i&#146;m not gonna see anybody else. are you-are you sure you don&#146;t want something more?", "answer": "  wow! i don&#146;t know, maybe. i&#146;m&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh-oh, rach! i was just messin&#146; around!  like you did last night when i had to pee?", "answer": "  i knew that! i knew that! i was just messin&#146; with you too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  okay. okay. because for a minute you said you&#133;", "answer": " oh no-no-no-no, no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " &#133;that you actually&#133;", "answer": " no that&#146;s just&#151;&#151;that&#146;s just &#145;cause i&#146;m such a good messer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " rach?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " the bathroom?", "answer": " right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " well i had a great time! learned how to bake, ate great food, that&#146;s the first a i&#146;ve gotten since seventh grade, and i didn&#146;t have to sleep with the teacher this time.", "answer": " oh, look! acting for beginners! want to feel good about yourself?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " what the hell!", "answer": " okay.  the acting teacher: all right, let&#146;s start with some basics. can anybody tell me what the difference between upstage and downstage is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep21.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}]